9-1-1, please
state your name.
Katherine Weaver.
What's the nature
of your emergency?
My ex-husband is
lurking outside our home.
Are you alone?
No, I am here with my son.
Has anyone been hurt?
No.
Has he threatened you
or made any attempt to force
his way into the premises?
No, but this is the third night
in a row that he's been here.
And what's he doing now?
He's sitting in his car.
Can you tell me how long
he's been out there?
No, I don't know how
long he's been out there.
And what's your
ex-husband wearing?
I don't know.
I can't see him.
You can't see him?
No, I can't see
his face, but-
- Without a positive ID
- we can't prioritize-
I understand officer,
but I'm telling you it's him.
Ma'am, I'd like you to
take a deep breath.
Don't tell me to
My ex-husband
is stalking us.
Is there a restraining order
against your ex-husband?
No, it's expired.
Without an actual
crime being committed,
I cannot prioritize an
officer to your location.
Mom?
Look, you know the drill.
I liked it there.
Yeah, I know. Me too.
You don't even know
if it was him.
Trust me, it was him.
Could've just been
some guy in a car.
At one in the morning,
three nights in a row.
It was him.
Hey, Cameron.
Cameron, honey.
Come on. Get up.
Where are we?
Hopefully somewhere
with decent coffee.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
-Hey.
What have I said
about social media?
Cameron, we've
been over this.
This is how he
found us last time.
They're my friends.
You will understand
when you're older.
That's what you always say.
Mom?
There's no one out there.
Looks like somebody
gotta good sleep.
Truce?
Games only. No texting.
Deal?
Deal.
So, I think I got
a lead on a place.
What do you think?
Rent's a bargain,
and it comes furnished.
Hmm?
Seriously?
Yeah. What?
I think it's perfect.
Ah! Just think of all the
fresh air and the scenery.
Beautiful fresh country air.
It's a farmhouse.
It's got character.
And besides, we'll be
safer in the country.
It's in the
middle of nowhere.
How am I supposed
to make friends?
You're gonna meet plenty
of kids at school.
And there's a
rec centre in town.
Yay.
Thank you.
Hey Alan.
Good to see ya.
Chloe, you're gettin'
prettier every day.
Ah, excuse me?
Would you happen
to be Katherine?
Are we, ah, that obvious?
It, uh, it's a small town.
I'm Ken Armstrong,
got your email.
Oh, it's nice to meet you.
Um, this is my son, Cameron.
Would you like to sit down?
Yeah, don't mind
if I do. Thanks.
Good potatoes, huh?
- Mornin' handsome.
- Hey Betty.
The usual?
Ah, no thanks,
I already ate,
but I'd love a
cup of coffee.
And you know what?
Put their breakfast
on my tab will ya?
Oh, no, that's-that's okay.
No, please.
It's my pleasure.
Will do.
Thank you.
That's very kind,
thank you.
So what brings you
two to Wolf Hollow?
Insanity.
-Pardon?
Um, we're just looking for
something simple, you know?
Bit of a slower pace.
The city can be a little
overwhelming. Right?
You've come to
the right place.
People around here
are pretty grounded.
Well, we're really
excited to see the house.
Right, Cameron?
That's the house?
Well, it doesn't
look like much,
but it's got good bones.
It's not like
we're buying it.
Ah, um, everything is
in good working order.
But on the off chance
you need a repair,
Art, the landlord is just
the next house over.
Come on, let me
show you around.
Come on in.
Huh?
Looks like it's been
vacant for a while?
You mean abandoned.
Living room is on the left
with a working fireplace.
Oh wow.
And you've got a good
sized kitchen here.
Decent amount of storage.
Lots of natural light.
And the appliances
are pretty much new.
Oh, I love a separate
dining room.
Yeah, it's great
for company.
Yeah.
There's a powder room
on the main floor too.
Oh, that's handy.
Huh?
Art tried to spruce
the place up a bit.
The formica it's timeless,
right?
It's classic.
Where does that go?
Mm, the basement.
Why is it locked?
Just as a precaution
against animals.
There's a lot of
raccoons in this part.
There's access to the
outside down there.
Hey, how 'bout I show
you the upstairs?
Do you know when
this place was built?
1869.
Wow.
Yeah, if these
walls could talk.
Is, uh, is that
water damage or...?
It's access to the attic.
Oh.
Seems kinda strange
that it's boarded up.
Well, I did it for safety.
You know, wouldn't want
anyone go exploring
and gettin' hurt.
Yeah.
Come on, lemme show you
the, uh, main bedroom.
It's, uh, it's
got a great view.
So this here is the master.
Not a bad size
for a house...
You ever see a sunset
over a cornfield?
Can't say that I have.
Well, you are in for a treat.
Hello?
Cameron.
Cameron?
I-I'm fine.
I just tripped.
Are you hurt?
I said I'm fine.
Oh wow.
Yeah. Yeah.
I spoke to Art and he
says he'll clean this up
by end of the week.
Oh, there's no rush.
What? We're staying?
Honey, of course
we're staying.
Well, uh, there's some
paperwork to do upstairs.
Aw, I've always loved
that photo of us.
Yeah.
Where's Cowboy Boots?
Cowboy Boots?
You mean Ken?
Yeah.
He just left.
He sounds like
an infomercial.
Mm, well, that infomercial
just let us move here
without a damage deposit.
And he told me his secretary
is going on mat leave.
So I might get a job.
Great.
Yeah, it is great.
We need the money.
Hmm.
Come here. Come here.
I know this
isn't easy for you.
And I wish it was different.
Believe me, I do.
But this is our life
and it doesn't
change the fact
that I love you more than
anything in the world.
I know.
Try to get some
good sleep, okay?
Cameron.
That's Cody Murphy,
world's biggest dickhead.
So what's your story?
My mom has a thing for
shitty little towns.
No offence taken.
Hello? I'm home.
Mom?
What are ya doin' down here?
It's dangerous if you
don't know your way around
all this crap.
Ken said you live
next farm over.
Look, if you're gonna
follow me around,
you may as well make
yourself useful.
Go on.
You need a hand with that?
It's okay.
Mm.
Did a kid live here?
A boy.
A long time ago.
Did you know him?
Mind your step.
Be easier if you
put it down.
What's his name?
Who's name?
The boy.
You ask a lot of questions,
you know that?
Mr. Sinclair?
You can call me Art.
Katherine.
Ah, Cameron,
honey, could you grab the
groceries from the car, please?
I didn't know you
were coming by today.
No, well, if it suits I'll
grab the rest tomorrow.
That's fine.
It's a nice place you got.
I should go.
I got chores.
You, ah, thank
your boy for me.
I will.
So, how was your
first day at school?
It's good.
Good?
Yeah, did you
make any friends?
Why would I?
We're just
gonna move again.
Well, I had a good day.
I spoke to Ken and
I got that job.
What?
As Ken's receptionist.
I told you, I...
It doesn't matter.
He didn't even ask
for any references.
And I start on Monday.
Isn't that great?
Yeah. That's great.
I gotta say, Ken has
really come through for us.
Could you...
Cameron.
Cameron. Cameron.
What're ya gonna do, man.
Bro, what is that?
Bro. Hey, you're
the new kid, right?
Heard you moved into
Sinclair's shithole.
So, have you heard 'em yet?
Heard what?
The dogs.
Oh you don't know?
They gutted their owner
right there on the lawn.
Ripped his throat out.
Rumour has it they
still haunt the place.
Where you goin' buddy?
If you're not too careful
they'll get you too.
A and J friends forever.
Mom?
You home?
Dad?
Hello? Anybody there?
You're not real.
Frank and Evelyn McTavish.
Jacky.
Cameron?
Do you think the real estate
office would have anything
about the history
of this house?
I dunno, maybe. Why?
For a history project.
I need to write about
something local.
But you know who you
might wanna ask is Art.
Mr. Sinclair.
He might be able to help
A and J.
I gotta go.
No.
NO!
Cameron?
Hey, what's the matter?
Who are you talking to?
He was in my room.
Who? Sweetheart. There's no-
He was right there!
There's no one here.
You were dreaming.
I'm serious.
Baby, we've been down
this road before.
It's been a stressful
three weeks, that's all.
You feel warm.
Coming down with something?
I dunno.
Cameron, you're burning up.
Hmm. You're still
a little warm.
I'll call Ken.
I'll tell him I
can't come in.
I'll be fine.
We're safer in the country.
Unless Dad's posing as a cow,
I think we're fine.
Fine.
I'll be home as soon as I can.
There's leftovers in the fridge.
And if you need anything,
you call me. Okay?
Yeah.
Love you.
Love you too.
It is been lonely since
mother and father left.
You're not real.
Mother left first.
That's why Father
got the dogs.
To keep the bad people away.
They're everywhere,
you know...
even when you
can't see them.
Sometimes people upset them.
That's when bad
things happen.
Hello? Mr. Sinclair?
Mr. Sinclair?
Is someone there?
Cameron.
You're not real.
Please don't be afraid.
Stop it!
You're not real.
None of this is real.
I'm real, Cameron.
I'm your friend.
You're not my friend!
Leave me alone!
Run!
He just got home.
Where were you?
You were supposed
to be home sick.
Look Cameron, I-I'm worried-
They're coming.
What?
Honey, stop it,
you're scaring me.
There's nothing out here.
Mom! No!
Stop! Cameron!
They were there.
I saw them.
What do you know
about Frank McTavish?
Same thing everyone knows.
He got killed
by his own dogs.
That's it?
Actually, they say that
Cody's great-grandmother
accused Frank McTavish of
murdering his own wife and kid.
There was this big
investigation and everything.
Okay. What happened?
They put her in a
mental hospital.
It turns out she lied
about the whole thing.
She's in the same care
home as my granddad.
My mom says she's crazy.
Obviously it runs
in the family.
You talkin' about me,
you little shit?
Leave him alone!
Mind your own
fucking business.
Beat his ass, Cody!
- They're fighting!
Kick his ass!
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's go, let's go!
You're dead, you little fuck!
That's enough!
I said that's enough!
You son of a bitch!
Both of you, come with me!
Suspended?
Mom, I swear it
wasn't my fault.
Just don't, Cameron.
I was defending myself.
I said don't.
Okay. Just...
this is how it
always starts.
How what starts?
Never mind.
No, tell me how
what starts?
Becoming like Dad?
Jacky, are you there?
You said I wasn't real.
I-I didn't mean it.
Can I show you something?
Arty and I used to play
here before Mother left.
Before Father got the dogs.
Sounds like you and
Arty were great friends.
He was always nice to me.
He understood.
Did your father ever
whoop you, Cameron?
My father whooped me,
but only when I deserved it.
He'd say,
This
is gonna hurt me...
more than it does you, boy
Cameron?
If only Mother was good
she wouldn't have gone away.
She wouldn't have gone away.
Father wouldn't
have got the dogs.
40s era music]
You think you can make
a fool outta me, huh?!
Is that what you think?!
Huh? Is that what you think?
Answer me! Answer me!
I
said answer me,
you goddamn whore.
Who do you think you are,
you can talk like
that to your husband?
You dirty fuckin' whore!
You coward!
Cameron?
Cameron?!
Stop, stop, stop, stop!
Honey, stop!
Stop, Cameron!
Stop it! Now, stop!
Stop, stop.
Mom?
- I'm here.
I'm here. I'm here.
It's okay. It's okay.
You're okay. You're okay.
You're okay. It's okay.
I'm here. I'm here.
Do you think I'm crazy?
No. Cameron, sweetie,
I-I've never thought
you were crazy.
You've been through a lot.
That's not your fault.
You think I'm
becoming like Dad?
No. Cameron, I am so sorry
that I said what I did.
You are a kind, bright young
man who cares about people.
But I think you
might need some help.
Your nightmares
are getting worse
and you're talking to
yourself again and I-
Plenty of people
talk to themselves.
People don't hurt
themselves, Cameron.
It's nothing to be ashamed
of but it's not normal.
I was talking to Ken and-
You talked to
Ken about this?
You had no right to
talk about my life!
Cameron, he is a good man
and he has become a friend.
Really? What else is he?
Okay, that is not fair.
Fair?
You wanna talk about fair?
How about dragging me
halfway across the country
in the middle of the night?
Cameron...
Is that fair?
Or telling me I just
need to make friends
and then the second I do,
telling me I
can't talk to them.
Cameron-
Is that fair to you?
Cameron...
All I ever hear is we have
to move because of Dad.
Well, maybe I want
him to find us
so he can take me
away from you.
Cam, you take that back.
Take it back.
Maybe I'm not the crazy one.
I hate this place!
I miss my dad.
Me too.
What are you doing here?
You shouldn't have come,
it's late.
Don't worry. Just grab
your boy and let's go.
I don't want him to hear us.
He's still up.
I don't care.
I'm not leaving you with him.
You have to go.
Mom?
Shhhh!
Cameron?
This way.
Jacky?
Over here. This way.
Hurry!
Cameron.
This way. Over here.
You're always rooting around.
What the hell you doing out
there in that clearing?
You aimin' to get
yourself killed? Hmm?
Don't you know it's the
middle of huntin' season?
I could've easily
mistook you for a deer.
I didn't know.
Anybody ever tell you
not to go pokin' around
other people's things?
Now let's go.
That clearing was special,
wasn't it?
To Jacky?
I ain't heard that
name in a long while.
Don't you want to
know what happened?
Why would I?
Because he was your friend.
Everybody has secrets, kid.
It'd be best to
leave this alone.
Now get outta here.
Hey.
Oh, thank you.
Took a wild guess
you'd want a burger.
No pickles.
Yeah.
So, tell me what
you're writing about.
Stuff.
Okay. What kind of stuff?
History stuff.
Yeah, I know,
but tell me what.
Cameron.
I don't want you to
freak out, okay?
Why would I freak out?
'Cause you're my mom.
That's what you do.
Okay. I promise I
will not freak out.
Okay.
You know the guy that I got
into a fight with at school?
Cody?
Yeah. I'm trying to forget.
Well, his great-grandmother
thinks that the guy who
used to live on our property,
Frank McTavish,
killed his wife, his kid,
and his wife's boyfriend.
Wow.
I was looking into it
'cause I'm thinking,
what if it's true?
What if he did kill them?
Then the bodies might be
hidden on our property.
That, okay, okay, Cameron.
That's enough. I can't
listen to anymore.
You said you
wouldn't freak out.
No, I'm, I'm
not freaking out.
I just...
Sweetie, I don't
think it's healthy
to be so emotionally invested
in something this disturbing.
This is why I never
tell you anything!
'Cause you promise
you're not gonna freak out
and then you do!
Cameron, lower your voice.
You never take
anything I say seriously.
Eat your burger.
Jacky?
Shh. It's okay, Buddy.
It's just me.
Dad?
Hey, I got a surprise for ya.
Come on.
I'm up here, Buddy.
Come on! Come on.
Your mother didn't
leave you after all, boy.
No!
I'm never far.
Okay, Buddy, I'm never far.
Cameron?
Come on. You don't
wanna be late
for your first day back.
Coming.
I still can't believe
you broke his nose.
Yeah.
Hey, do you think Cody's
great-grandmother
still remembers what
happened to Frank McTavish?
I dunno. Why?
Hey, but where are you going?
I know I love her,
but $5,000 for her vet?
Come in.
Mrs. Murphy?
Who are you?
A friend of Cody's.
My Cody?
Yeah, we're working
together on a history project.
Oh. Well, come in, come in.
You have a lot of photos.
Uh huh.
Cody told me about
your brother.
Shhh.
We mustn't speak
about Matthew.
It's okay, I won't tell.
Is he in any of these photos?
Why do you wanna
know about Matthew?
Who are you?
Where do you live?
I said, where do you live, boy?!
Frank McTavish
killed my brother.
He killed them all!
Shh! Mrs. Murphy, it's okay.
I know what I know!
I believe you.
I believe Matthew
was murdered.
Don't you lie to me!
Do you think I'm crazy?!
Who are you?!
I just wanted information.
He's dead.
Do you hear me?
They're all dead!
What's going on here?
Hey!
How was your first
day back at school?
Good.
Really?
Because I got a call
from the secretary
who said you didn't
show up today.
Where the hell were you,
Cameron?
And don't lie to me!
We are not done.
Mrs. Weaver?
Yes?
I'm Officer Culp.
May I come in?
Of course.
Is...
Is this about
my ex-husband?
I'm afraid it's
about your son.
Is she gonna be okay?
Well, she won't be
walking without her crutches
anytime soon,
but she'll be all right.
Do we need a lawyer?
No one is pressing
charges at the moment.
No one wants that.
But they do want the truth.
So how about you tell us
what you were doing there?
I wanted to know the
truth about Frank McTavish.
Mrs. Murphy thinks
Frank McTavish
killed his family
and Matthew Fraser.
Well, Ms. Murphy has a
delicate grasp of reality.
She's right.
I saw them.
You saw who?
Matthew Fraser and
Mrs. McTavish.
Officer, I am sorry.
Cameron's imagination-
Not my imagination!
Their bodies are
in the attic!
What?
You can't possibly
know that.
Our attic is sealed.
I saw it in my dream.
Oh my God, Cameron.
No. You need to listen
to me for once.
Katherine?
Hey.
Hey, Janis. I saw
your car out front.
Is everything, uh,
is everything okay?
Cameron thinks that we
have dead bodies in our-
We do!
Oh my God, Cameron.
Do you not get this?
I've never seen this
guy before in my life!
This is what Jacky
was trying to tell me!
Jacky? Who the hell is Jacky?
That Matthew Fraser and
Mrs. McTavish were murdered
and their bodies
are in the attic.
Oh my God, Cameron,
I think you need to stop.
Why can't you
just believe me?
If you don't believe me,
just go in the attic
and check it out
for yourself.
Cameron, enough!
I'm telling you
they're up there.
Whoa. Whoa. Hey, hey.
Why don't we all
just take a breath?
Okay?
Why don't we just go
take a look in the attic.
I mean, maybe he's right.
Tell me that you
don't actually believe
that we have
bodies up there.
No, it's-it's not
about what I believe,
it's about what
Cameron believes.
Until he sees for himself,
it's gonna be on his mind.
So, I dunno,
what do you think, Janis?
Should we take a look?
Yeah. Yeah, let's
check it out.
Hey Art, it's Ken Armstrong.
Yep. I got it. I got it.
Well, no, no. It's a
potential crime scene.
I better go first.
Well, it's all yours.
Have a good look.
It can't be.
Do you see?
It was just a dream.
You said it yourself.
I-I know-I know
they were here.
Someone-someone must
have moved them.
Maybe McTavish figured he
couldn't keep them up here.
Your father knew him.
Maybe he helped get
rid of the bodies.
I am so sorry.
Cameron is not well.
He doesn't...
Honey, you don't know
what you're saying.
Shut up!
I do know what
I'm saying!
No matter what I do
you think I'm crazy!
Well, I'm not!
Okay! I'm not!
You're not my fucking dad!
Cameron. Hey. Hey.
It's okay. Shh.
It's all right.
Easy, easy, easy, easy.
I set up the cot
upstairs in the big room.
Ken's gonna stay
with us tonight.
Why?
Because you're scared of me?
No Cameron,
I'm scared for you.
This is all my fault.
I should have seen it coming.
I think it's best if you
stay home from school
for the next few days.
Seriously?
-Yeah.
Until this settles down.
This is a small town and this
kind of thing can get around
and we don't need that
kind of attention.
Not with him out
there looking.
You can't even say his name.
I'll figure it out
with your school
and I'll make sure
to get your homework
and I'll talk to your history
teacher about your essay.
There's no essay.
You get some rest.
Hey, good morning.
Like bacon and eggs?
Sure.
Go ahead.
I'm sorry about last night.
Hey, don't worry about it.
Really.
I really thought
they were there.
Mm-hmm.
I feel like an idiot.
Look, I've been sure about
a lot of things in my life
that did not turn out
the way I expected.
There's nothing
wrong with that.
So you have kids?
I do. Tyler and Sophia.
You miss them?
Every single day.
I get to see 'em
every other weekend.
Christmas, a couple
days at Thanksgiving.
But, uh, they're doing
things that I'm not part of
and making memories
that I'll never share.
It's hard.
How much did Mom
tell you about Dad?
Cameron, whatever
it is between you,
your mom and your dad,
that's your business.
If you wanna
tell me or not,
it's up to you.
But just know that I'm...
I'm here.
Can I show you
something after?
Sure.
I'm no expert, but these
look like a cry for help.
You say you found them
in the coal room?
Uh huh.
See the dogs?
Mm-hmm.
And look, Jacky's mother is
missing from most of them.
Things just kind of got bigger
and bigger in your head, huh?
Mom thinks I'm crazy.
No. No. She doesn't
think you're crazy.
She's just worried about you.
I-I see him all the time
and I think he wanted to
show me these drawings.
I think he's trying
to tell me something.
So I, um, I spoke with
your principal today.
Under the circumstances
she thinks that it's, um,
best if you and Cody are kept
apart for the time being.
So, I'm gonna be driving
you to school from now on.
Okay.
Um...
also, Ken has agreed
to, ah, stay with us
just until things
settle down.
And, um, I have asked him to
make an appointment for you
to talk to a therapist
friend of his.
She's really very good,
Cameron.
Um, I think it-
You told her?
Cameron, I had to.
Ken was only trying to help.
Cameron, he cares about you.
You don't get it.
It's you he cares about!
You!
You don't think I
didn't see him
sneaking into your
room last night?
I might have problems,
but I'm not an idiot!
Hello?
Buddy, is that you?
Mike.
Hey, don't hang up, please.
It's you, isn't it?
Yeah. Dad, it's me.
I always knew you'd call.
Ah, I didn't know when,
but I-I knew you would.
Sorry it took so long.
Hey, don't be sorry.
Don't...
don't you be sorry, ah,
we're talking now, right?
Yeah.
How...
How's my boy, huh?
How's my boy?
You good? You okay?
I'm okay.
Well, you...
you don't,
I hate-I hate to say it,
but you-you
don't sound okay.
Yeah.
Dad, were you parked
outside our house?
What do you...
what are you talking about?
Have you been...
stalking us?
Buddy, your mom,
she has issues, okay?
And I really don't like
saying that to you,
but it-it's true.
Okay?
So was it?
No, it-it wasn't,
it wasn't me, Buddy.
Okay?
But you know, hey,
if it was,
could you blame me?
I mean, you're my son.
I just miss the hell...
I just miss the
hell out of you, Buddy.
I miss you too.
Yeah.
- Cameron?
- I gotta go.
Hey Cam, could you just,
if you wait a second-
Hey, who are you talking to?
No one.
It's gonna be okay.
Whatever.
Why won't you look
at me, Cameron?
'Cause you're not real.
I'm right here.
All right.
If you're real,
I want answers.
Okay.
Where are you when
I'm not around?
I-I don't know.
Why are you
asking me that?
'Cause everyone
thinks I'm crazy!
I'm starting to
think they're right.
You're not crazy, Cameron.
Stop pretending
to be my friend!
I am your friend.
If you're my friend...
tell me what happened the
night your mother left.
Jacky, hand me that suitcase.
The empty one. Hurry!
Get up to the attic, boy.
Now!
Don't! Don't you
come near me!
I've had enough!
You can't stop me.
You slut.
You run around like
a goddamn whore!
You oughta be
ashamed of yourself.
But you ain't.
You ain't sorry.
I'll make you sorry.
Don't you touch me!
Stop! Don't touch me!
Stop!
He said Mother left and
wouldn't be coming back.
Then he grabbed a shovel,
worked the rest of the day
in the barn.
He wouldn't let me leave
the house after that.
He said if people knew
I was on the farm
without a mother,
they'd take me away.
That's why he got the dogs,
to keep the bad people away.
But I had to tell
Arty I was okay.
I didn't want him to worry.
So you met him
in the clearing?
I made him swear
to keep my secret.
And he did too.
But then Father found out.
It's all my fault.
What's your fault?
Hey, I've been calling you.
Dinner's ready.
-Sorry.
Hey.
Come on.
Your dinner's getting cold.
Hey, Buddy.
Glad you called me back.
How you doing?
Everything okay?
Hey Dad, I wanna
ask you something.
Shoot.
Promise you won't
think I'm crazy?
No, phsst, why
would I think that?
Because everyone else does.
Well, I'm not everyone else.
I'm your dad and I love
you very much, Buddy.
Do you believe in ghosts?
Sure. Yeah, why not?
I mean, ah, look,
I've-I've never seen one,
I've never talked to one.
But, ah, loads of people
claim they have
and they can't all
be liars, right?
Yeah.
Cameron?
Dad, I gotta go.
Ken's calling.
Who's Ken?
I gotta go.
Wait, Cameron-
-Bye.
Hey.
Everything okay up here?
Yeah. Why?
I just, ah, wondering
who you were talking to.
I wasn't talking to anyone.
Okay.
Look, it's getting dark.
Don't stay up too late, okay?
Are you gonna tell my mom?
Tell her what?
He seems really nice.
Not like my father.
He's not my father.
Jacky, what happened
to your dad?
Why was it your fault?
He told me not
to wander off.
Not to go to the
clearing to see Arty.
If only I'd listened.
No!
You think you can
disobey me, boy?
disobey me, huh?
Run off to the woods?
I thought I told you
to stay in the house!
No! No!
I'll feed you to
the dogs, boy.
That'll teach you, huh?
No, no! Please!
When they tear you
apart like rabbits.
No!
Hey, hey!
Hey, that'll teach ya.
That'll teach ya-
Papa!
Help me, boy!
Cameron, I owe
you an apology.
You trusted me
with something
and I told your mom.
I should have been
clear with you
that I was gonna tell
her and explained why.
I'm sorry.
Sweetheart, I'm,
ah, I'm sorry too.
I should have told
you about me and Ken.
We shouldn't have
been sneaking around.
And if you would rather
I stay at my place,
it's totally cool.
You can stay
here if you want.
Yeah? Thanks.
Hey, how about, ah, from
here on in no more secrets.
Someone's in the barn.
Your father?
No. Maybe Cody.
Cameron.
Honey, are you sure it wasn't
just your imagination?
I don't know.
I only saw him
for a second.
I got an idea.
How about we go
check it out?
You seen him in
the loft, right?
Yeah.
Brrr! It's cold up here!
You see anything?
No. Do you?
No.
Feel better?
I feel stupid.
Hey, hey.
There's no shame
in being afraid.
You know how scared I was
the first time we had
a real conversation?
You were scared of me?
Mm-hmm.
I figured if you hated me,
I was toast with your mom.
Come on.
It's too cold up here.
Stay off our property.
What?
Get outta my face
ya little shit.
I know you were in our barn.
Go ahead, do something.
I'm warning you, Cody.
Stay away from my house.
No wonder everybody
thinks you're crazy.
Hey, Buddy.
Hey, Dad.
So what happened to
you the other night?
You had me worried.
Sorry. Someone
came in the barn.
Someone?
Let me guess...
it was Ken?
Yeah. It-it's just...
I don't think we should
be talking right now.
Who says? Your mother?
No. Me.
I-I just don't like
going behind her back.
It's nothing you did,
I swear.
Don't let her push
you around, son.
She does that.
No, I-I told you.
It's not Mom.
It's just...
I don't like sneaking around.
It'll be different
when I'm older.
Like I said,
I'm not gonna call anymore.
Well, Buddy,
you do what you
have to do and,
well, I'll do
what I have to do.
I gotta go.
Dad?
Hey, Buddy. Look at you.
Dad, what are
you doing here?
Well, I, ah, I drove
up a few days ago.
I'm staying at a
motel in town.
It's a decent room.
Coffee's crap.
Okay.
Dad, what are you
doing in Ken's car?
Geez. Not even a
'Hey, how ya doing?'
Dad, where's Ken?
Hop in and I'll tell ya.
Buddy, I said hop in.
Cameron, is that you, buddy?
I'm afraid your mom can't
come to the phone right now.
She got held up.
Okay.
If you ever wanna
see your mother again,
I suggest you give me your
phone and get in the car.
Where's Mom and Ken?
Again with Ken.
Seriously, Buddy.
I mean, your mother
I understand.
Where are they?!
Okay. Okay. Calm down. Geez.
Your mom's back
at the house.
Is she okay?
She's fine.
I mean, she did take a pretty
nasty tumble down the stairs,
but she's gonna
be all right.
I actually had to lock
her in the basement.
She's feisty, your mother,
I'll give her that.
What about Ken?
He's hog-tied in the trunk.
He was kicking
around back there,
but whack to the head
knocked some sense into him.
That was you last night.
In the barn.
Oooh, shoot.
Yeah. Yeah. That was...
Yeah, ya got me.
How'd you know?
I guess, well, doesn't
really matter now, but...
What are you gonna do?
Kill us?
Well, Kenny Boy,
he's gotta pay and
once he does, then it'll
just be the three of us.
But your mother, you know,
she's always made me do things
that I don't want to do,
and she'll never
take me back
and she won't
let me have you.
And that,
that's not fair, is it?
Of course, she's
gonna start begging.
But your mom, she's...
she's always tried
to make me feel bad.
Shift the blame.
Hey. Hey, don't worry, Buddy.
I don't want you to worry.
Okay? I...
I don't think a boy
should see his mother die.
Okay?
That wouldn't be right.
Cam, stop!
Cam!
Just stop! Cam!
Goddamnit!
Cam! Cam!
Goddamnit.
Cameron!
Don't make this harder
than it has to be!
You know I'm
gonna find you.
Cameron!
Cameron, come back, Buddy.
Let's, let's just start over.
Jacky.
Cameron!
Jacky, where do I go?
Cameron?!
Over here! This way!
Buddy.
Buddy!
I'm not gonna let
you get away again.
Come here!
No!
-Okay.
Get away from me!
Come on!
Stop!
I'm your dad. I love you!
No you don't!
Okay. Alright. Stop! Stop!
Just stop!
Please, Dad. Please don't.
Please. Dad, don't shoot.
Okay, okay.
I gotcha. I gotcha. Shh.
Okay, I've gotcha.
He was mauled by something.
What? I don't know
'cause we haven't seen wolves
in these parts for years.
But we'll have to
wait for forensics.
His isn't the only
body out there.
What?
Cameron...
That boy you
asked me about...
the one who grew
up in this house.
Jacky?
He's buried out
there in that clearing.
How do you know that?
'Cause I buried him.
We were just boys the
last time I saw him.
I knew what his
father was like.
He was a lot like
your father.
I saw the bruises.
I kept that promise to Jacky
'cause I was afraid for him.
McTavish got the
dogs shortly after
and within a couple
months he was dead so...
When Jacky didn't turn up,
I figured his mother must
have come back for him.
Oh, about 10 years ago
there was a bad storm.
Blew some shingles
off the roof.
So I went up into the attic
to check on the damage.
And I found Jacky curled
up in a old chest.
Must'a crawled inside,
tryin' to hide
and got trapped.
I should have gone
to the police.
But no one was
looking for him.
And he'd been dead
more than 20 years so...
buried him out there
in that clearing.
The one place I knew
he'd been happy.
And for what it's worth,
I think that Frank McTavish
murdered his wife
and Matthew Fraser.
Well without a body we
can't prove it was homicide.
They're in the barn.
Jacky told me after
his mom went away,
his dad took a shovel and
spent the rest of the day
working in the barn.
Cameron, honey, it's been-
They're in there.
Trust me.
Jacky?
I'm going to go.
I just wanted to
say thanks...
for everything.